There's nothing sadder than a puppet without a ghost.
Ghost in the Shell is a science fiction, drama,
action film directed by Rupert Sanders.
In the near future, Major is the first of her kind: a human saved from a terrible crash, then
cyber-enhanced to be a perfect soldier devoted to stopping the world's most dangerous criminals.
Major Mira Killian / Motoko Kusanagi, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Aramaki, played by Takeshi Kitano.
Batou, played by Pilou Asbæk.
Kuze, played by Michael Pitt.
Togusa, played by Ng Chin Han.
Dr. Ouelet, played by Juliette Binoche.
Ghost in the Shell is a 2017 cyberpunk action film directed by Rupert Sanders
and written by Jamie Moss, William Wheeler, and Ehren Kruger.
It is the first live-action movie based on the Japanese Ghost in the Shell franchise envisioned by Masamune Shirow, and
stars Scarlett Johansson, Takeshi Kitano, Michael Pitt, Pilou Asbæk, Chin Han, and Juliette Binoche.
Set in a near future when the line between humans and robots is blurring, the story follows
Major Mira Killian (Johansson), a cyborg supersoldier who investigates her past.
Filming for Ghost in the Shell took place in New Zealand at Stone Street Studiosfrom
February to June 2016, with additional filming in Hong Kong that June.
The film premiered in Tokyo on March 16, 2017, and was released in the
United States on March 31, 2017, in IMAX, 3D, IMAX 3D, and 4DX.
It grossed $169.8 million worldwide against a production budget of $110 million, and lost at least $60
million (with more than $100 million being a possibility due to a disputed budget).
On home media, however, the film debuted at number two.
Ghost in the Shell received mixed reviews, with praise for its cast performances, visual style, action sequences,
cinematography and musical score, but criticism for its plot and lack of character development.
The casting of non-Asian actors (particularly Johansson in the lead role) drew accusations of racism and whitewashing in the United
States, although Mamoru Oshii, the director of the original anime, stated that there was no basis for this accusation.
The film explores themes of strong woman, hacker, philosophy, cyborg, dystopia.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.